softperfect.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy

At SoftPerfect, your security and privacy is of the utmost importance to us. This policy describes how we collect, use and protect your personal information.

## Contact information

We collect basic contact information that you choose to provide when you contact us. This information is used for administrative purposes only and is not shared with our partners or third parties. When contacting us with general questions, not related to a particular purchase or transaction, you can do so without providing any personal information.

## Purchases

When you purchase a product from us, your payment is processed by [PayPro](https://payproglobal.com/) via secure payment gateway. Both your personal data and payment details, including credit card number where applicable, are encrypted as they traverse the Internet from you to PayPro directly. PayPro then shares partial payment information (such as the last 4 digits of the credit card number) and your contact details with us, which we use for issuing a software licence to you. After that, your details are kept in a secure database for ongoing support purposes only.

Your can ask us to delete the information we hold about you if you agree that this will make any further support of your software licence impossible. Your licence will continue working as before, but we will not be able to assist you with any matter that requires identifying your purchase. For example, we will not be able to recover your licence key if you lose it, or provide licence renewal discounts.

## E-mails and marketing

We never send any unsolicited or marketing e-mails.

## General information

We collect general, non-personal information about visitors to our website. This information is collected for creating a broad picture of our visitors to continually refine our products and services; it cannot be used to identify any particular individual.
